<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../input-cache/schemas/R5/fhir-single.xsd">
  <!-- The spaces between the open and close "a" tag are mandatory.  (Cuz HTML renderers are dumb...) -->
  <a name="intro"> </a>
  <h3>Introduction</h3>
	<p>
    Provides FHIR guidance for applying security labels with coded tags for use in access control systems governing the collection, access, use, and disclosure of the target FHIR Resource(s) as required by applicable organizational, jurisdictional, or personal "sharing with protection" policies.
  </p>
	<a name="technical"> </a>
	<h3>Technical Overview</h3>
	<p>
    Provides FHIR guidance on:
    <ul>
        <li>
          How to select a security label based on the HL7 Privacy and Security Healthcare Classification System (HCS) label adjudication algorithms, the value in establishing consensus on a default security label for representing policies or consent directives within an exchange ecosystem, and the value of establishing default security labels for information exchanged within the Trust Framework of a policy domain.
        </li>
        <li>
        How an Access Control System, such as an OAuth Authorization Server can use the security labels to filter responses to person/population based queries and pushed disclosures that meets:
        <ul>
          <li>
            Authorization Requirements specifying control over whether or not a client’s request for import or export of person/population Resources will be permitted
          </li>
          <li>
            Filtering Requirements specifying, at a more fine-grained level, what resources will appear in the results of a person/population export or accepted in an import operation, including approaches to filtering for the minimum necessary information based on policy.
          </li>
          <li>
            Transformation Requirements specifying the requirements for applying functions on imported or exported person/population Resources, which modify and transform the content of any Resource per applicable privacy/security policies and/or data subject's(s') consent directive
          </li>
          <li>
            Provenance Requirements specifying the recording and consumption of provenance information in a person/population Resource(s) export or import operation.
          </li>
        </ul>
      </li>
      </ul>
      Describes how to structure FHIR meta.security to meet the HL7 Healthcare Privacy and Security Classification System syntactic and semantic rules to convey computable and interoperable policy within a policy domain by use of Trust Contracts with binding capability statements.

      Describes the use of FHIR meta.security extensions to enable specification of the manner in which security label "privacy marks" are rendered, e.g., per CUI requirements; reference policy, contract, or consent directive instances; indicate the authority responsible for the assigned security label; and indicate whether a label has been upgraded, downgraded, or declassified, and the party responsible for doing so.
  </p>
  <a name="walkthrough"> </a>
  <p>
    The main sections of this IG are:
  </p>
  <ul>
    <li>
      <a href="background.html">Background</a> - provides business context for the implementation guide and information that implementers should be
      familiar with before reading the remainder of the IG.  There could be multiple pages for this.
    </li>
    <li>
      <a href="spec.html">Detailed Specification</a> - The actual stuff implementers are expected to do.  (Could be multiple pages for this.)
    </li>
    <li>
      <a href="downloads.html">Downloads</a> - Allows downloading a copy of this implementation guide and other useful information
    </li>
  </ul>
</div>